Guide to the F. Curtis Michel Scientist-Astronaut Papers, 1951-1981 MS 043
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II. NASA Papers, c. 1963-1981, 230181; 65 boxes
  - Subseries H: Apollo Training, 230617
    - Crew Systems Study Slide, September 1, 1965; 230682 (Box 17)
    - Electrical Power System Study Guide, August 1, 1965; 230681 (Box 17)
    - Electrical Power System Study Guide, October 1, 1965; 230680 (Box 17)
    - Electrical Power System Study Guide, March 15, 1966; 230679 (Box 17)
    - AS-201 Mission Rules, August 1, 1965; 230678 (Box 17)
    - AS-201 Mission Rules, Rev. A, November 1, 1965; 230677 (Box 17)
    - AS-201 Technical Information Summary, January 17, 1966; 230676 (Box 17)
    - AS-202 Technical Information Summary, May 5, 1966; 230675 (Box 17)
    - AS-203 Technical Information Summary, June 14, 1966; 230674 (Box 17)
    - Apollo 278 Plan and Compatibility Analysis, July 15, 1966; 230673 (Box 17)
    - Apollo 5 Technical Information Summary, December 15, 1967; 230672 (Box 17)
    - Apollo 6 Technical Information Summary, March 1, 1968; 230671 (Box 17)
    - Apollo 12 Lunar Surface Operations Plan, October 23, 1969; 230670 (Box 18)
    - Apollo 12 Final Flight Plan, Rev. A., October 29, 1969; 230669 (Box 18)
    - Apollo 12 Final Flight Plan, Rev. B., November 4, 1969; 230668 (Box 18)
    - Apollo Command/Service Systems Handbook, AS-202, August 13, 1965; 230667 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Command Service Module Systems Handbook, CSM 101, April 7, 1967; 230666 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Spacecraft Console Drawing; Panels and Systems Drawings, 1966; 230665 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Data Package for AAP Modification Kit T-1 Audio Hardline, August 1967; 230664 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Critical Design Review, Phase 2, December 1965; 230663 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Critical Design Review, Number 3 Phase II Appendix V, December 1965; 230662 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Block II CSM, LEM and EVA Prime Comm. Links, 1966?; 230661 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Apollo Operations Handbook, CSM, April 16, 1966; 230660 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Apollo Operations Handbook, CSM, September 16, 1966; 230659 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Apollo Operations Handbook, CSM, Vol. I, October 17, 1966; 230658 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Apollo Operations Handbook, CSM, Vol. II, October 17, 1966; 230657 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Apollo Operations Handbook, CSM, November 12, 1966; 230656 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Apollo Operations Handbook, CSM, Changes, November 30, 1966; 230655 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Unified S-Band Telecommunications Techniques for Apollo, Vol. 1, March, 1965; 230654 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Telecommunication Systems Study Guide, March 3, 1965; 230653 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Telecommunication Systems Study Guide, October 1, 1965; 230652 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Telecommunication Subsystem Study Guide, November 15, 1965; 230651 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Apollo Systems Engineering Manual, Communications Subsystem Block II, September 15, 1966; 230650 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Univac 1106/1108 Exec 2 User's Manuals, July 1966; 230649 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Introduction to Computers, n.d.; 230648 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Apollo Guidance and Navigation System, April 9, 1965; 230647 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Apollo Navigation, Guidance, and Control Systems, May 1965, July 1966; 230646 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Apollo Guidance and Navigation System Study Guide, Block II Familiarization, September 1, 1966; 230645 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Apollo Guidance and Navigation System Study Guide, June 1, 1966; 230644 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Guidance and Control Division Presentation to President's Scientific Advisory Committee, May 7, 1965; 230643 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Block II SCS [Spacecraft Control System] Handout, September 26, 1966; 230642 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Stabilization and Control System Study Guides, March and September 1965; 230641 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Stabilization and Control Subsystem Study Guide, January 18, 1966; 230640 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Stabilization and Control System Block II Familiarization Briefing, 230639 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - LEM Environmental Control Subsystem Study Guide, March 10, 1966; 230638 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - LEM Structures and Mechanical System Study Guide, April 1, 1966; 230637 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - LEM Orientation Lesson Plans and Student Handout, April 12 and 13, 1966; 230636 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - LEM Electrical Power Subsystem Study Guide, July 8, 1966; 230635 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - LM Control Electronics Section and Abort Guidance Section Study Guide, September 27, 1966; 230634 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Propulsion Systems Student Study Guide, Part I, March 29, 1965; 230633 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Propulsion Systems, Student Study Guide, Part I, September 1, 1965; 230632 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - SPS [Service Propulsion System] Material, n.d.; 230631 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Rocket Performance and Propellants; Propulsion Systems Material, 230630 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Sequential Events Control System (LES, EDS and ELS) Study Guide, April 20, 1965; 230629 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Sequential Events Control System Study Guide (LES, EDS, ELS), August 20, 1965; 230628 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Sequential Events Control System Study Guide (LES, EDS, ELS), July 20, 1966; 230627 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Structures and Mechanical Systems, April 1, 1965; 230626 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Structures and Mechanical Subsystems, April 1, 1966; 230625 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - S-IVB Airlock, June 17, 1966; 230624 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Saturn IB/V Launch Vehicle Familiarization, May 1966; 230623 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Saturn V Flight Manual, April 1, 1968; 230622 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - S-IVB Workshop Material and Notes, June-November 1966; 230621 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Orbital Workshop Astronaut Review Outline, April 24, 1967; 230620 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - S-IVB Orbital Workshop Advance Data Package for Preliminary Design Review, May 1967; 230619 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - MSFC Orbital Workshop Astronaut Review Outline and Review Material, May 1967; 230618 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Subseries I: Gemini Program, 230608
    - Gemini Fact Sheets and Educational Material, 1965-1966; 230616 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Gemini Flight Summary Report, Missions 1-7, and Change Sheet, Missions 1-11, July 1966 November 1966; 230615 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Gemini Mission Charts [Orbital Maps], Gemini 6-9, 1965-1966; 230614 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Gemini Mid-program Conference, February 23-25, 1966; 230613 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Waste Management: Project Gemini, 1966?; 230612 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Gemini Experiments Correspondence, 1964-1965; 230611 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Gemini Experiments Correspondence, January-August 1966; 230610 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Gemini Experiments Status Reviews, December 1964-November 1965; 230609 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Subseries J: D.O.D. [Department of Defense] Experiments Folder, 230543
    - D-1: Basic Photography, January-August 1965; 230607 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - D-2: Photographic Definition of Objects in Near Proximity in Space, November 1964-January 1965; 230606 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - D-3: Mass Determination, September 1964-January 1965; 230605 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - D-4: Radiometric Observations, March-April 1965; 230604 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - D-5: Star Occultation Measurements, June 1964-July 1965; 230603 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - D-8: Radiation Measurements, March-October 1964; 230602 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - D-9: Nuclear Emulsion, November 1964-August 1965; 230601 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - D-10: Navigation, March-November 1964; 230600 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - D-12: Modular Maneuvering Unit, April 1964-October 1965; 230599 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - D-12: Model Specification for Modular Maneuvering Unit Backpack, March 1965; 230598 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - D-13: Gemini In Flight Visual Acuity Experiment, July-December 1964; 230597 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - D-14: UHF-VHF Polarization, July-September 1965; 230596 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - D-15: Low Light Level Television, October 1964-January 1965; 230595 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - D-16: Minimum Reaction Power Tool Evaluation, June 1964 - August 1965; 230594 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - E-Retired, July 1964?-May 1965; 230593 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - T-2: Manual Space Navigation Sightings, August 1964-August 1965; 230592 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Gemini-Flown, August-November 1964; 230591 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - GTA-6 Experiments, July-September 1965; 230590 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - GT-7 Experiments, April 1964-October 1965; 230589 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - GTA-8 Experiments, February 1964-October 1965; 230588 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - GTA-9 Experiments, September 1963-May 1964; 230587 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - GTA-10 Experiments, August 1964; 230586 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - GTA-11 Experiments, July-October 1964; 230585 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - GTA-12 Experiments, December 1964; 230584 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Medical Experiments, April 1964-October 1965; 230583 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - M-1: Cardiovascular Reflex Conditioning, October 1963-February 1965; 230582 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - M-2: Cardiovascular Effects of Space Flight, February 1964; 230581 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - M-3: In-Flight Exercise (Work) Tolerance, February 1964-February 1965; 230580 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - M-4: In-Flight Phonocardiogram, February 1964-February 1965; 230579 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - M-5: Biochemical Analysis of Body Fluids (Plasma and Urine) and M-5A: Adaptation to Circadian Disrhythmia, December 1964-October 1965; 230578 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - M-6(A): Bone Demineralization During Weightlessness, February 1964-December 1965; 230577 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - M-7: Gemini Calcium Balance Study, February 1964-March 1965; 230576 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - M-8: In-Flight Electroencephalogram (EEG), February-September 1965; 230575 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - M-9: Gemini Vestibular Function Experiment, February 1964-July 1965; 230574 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - M-11: Cytogenetic and Immunological Studies of Blood, 1965; 230573 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - M-13: Measurement of Limb and Digit Volume and Pulse, 230572 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - M-14: Arterial Oxygen Saturation, Ear Pulse and Blood Content During Launch and Re-entry by Miniature Ear Oximeter, April 1964; 230571 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - M-15: Higher Mental Functions in Orbital Flight, May 1964; 230570 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - M-17: In-Flight Thoracic Bloodflow Determination, December 1965; 230569 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - M-18: In-Flight Vector Cardiogram, February 1965; 230568 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - M-20: In-Flight Pulmonary Function Studies, February 1965; 230567 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - MSC-2: Proton/Electron Spectrometer, August 1964-July 1965; 230566 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - MSC-3: Tri-Axis Flux Gate Magnetometer, August 1964; 230565 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - MSC-4: Optical Communication, October 1964-October 1965; 230564 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - MSC-5: UV Spectral Reflectance of the Lunar Surface, June 1964; 230563 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - MSC-6: Beta Spectrometer, May 1964-July 1965; 230562 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - MSC-7: A Gemini Bremestrahlung Spectrometer, May 1964-July 1965; 230561 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - MSC-8(A): Color Patch Photography, May-September 1965; 230560 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - MSC-11: Manual Space Navigation Sightings, 1964?; 230559 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - MSC-12: Landmark Contrast Measurement, October 1964-September 1965; 230558 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - MSFC-2: Thermal Control Coatings, July 1965; 230557 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - S-1: Zodiacal Light Photography, April 1964-June 1965; 230556 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - S-3: Frog Egg Growth, August 1964-September 1965; 230555 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - S-5: Synoptic Terrain Photography, January-September 1964; 230554 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - S-6: Synoptic Weather Photography, April 1964; 230553 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - S-7: Cloud-Top Altitutde Spectrograph, March 1963-April 1964; 230552 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - S-8 (D-13): Gemini In-Flight Visual Acuity, July 1964-November 1965; 230551 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - S-9: Nuclear Emulsion, 1958-1968; 230550 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - S-10: Agena Micrometeorite Collector, August-October 1965; 230549 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - S-11: Airglow Horizon Photography, June 1964-April 1967; 230548 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - S-12: Collection of Micrometeorites, November 1963-July 1965; 230547 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - S-13: Astronomical Observation with a Small Ultraviolet Camera, March 1964-June 1965; 230546 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - S-14: Orbital Otolith Experiment, December 1965; 230545 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - S-Retired, July 1963-March 1964; 230544 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Subseries K: Program Support Requirements Document, 230538
    - Book I, January 1966; 230542 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Book II, January 1966; 230541 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Book III, January 1966; 230540 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Book IIIA, Orbital - ATDA, January 29, 1966; 230539 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Subseries L: Apollo Program, 230370
    - Sub-subseries 1: Memoranda and Correspondence, 230514
      - Apollo Memoranda, 1965-1966; 230537 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Apollo Memoranda, January-February 1967; 230536 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Apollo Memoranda, March-May 1967; 230535 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Apollo Memoranda, June-December 1967; 230534 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Apollo Memoranda, 1968-1969; 230533 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Apollo Airlock, 1965; 230532 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Apollo 12 Press Kits, November 5, 1969 and n.d.; 230531 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - On the Moon with Apollo 15, June 1971; 230530 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - On the Moon with Apollo 16, April 1972; 230529 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - CCB [Configuration Control Board], June-September 1965; 230528 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Contributions of Manned Spacecraft Center Personnel to the Manned Lunar Exploration Symposium, June 15-16, 1964; 230527 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Flight Crew Memoranda, July 1964-May 1966; 230526 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Infrared Astronomy Program for Airplanes, September 1966; 230525 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Lunar Receiving Laboratory Facility Description, September 1968; 230524 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Lunar Surface Activities, July -October 1966; 230523 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Manned Photographic Telescope of the Goddard Space Astronomy Program, April 12, 1966; 230522 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Major NASA Launches, March, June 1965; 230521 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - The Meteoroid Environment of Project Apollo, January 31, 1963; 230520 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Planetology Subcommittee, 1966; 230519 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Preliminary Mission Definition for Post-Apollo Manned Exploration of Space: Manned Earth Orbital Missions, November 1965; 230518 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Radiation Sources Associated with Apollo Spacecraft Operations, April 15, 1966; 230517 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - SA-503 Flight Operations Plan Meeting, December 9, 1966; 230516 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - The SPOC Story: Spacecraft Oceanography Project, June 1966; 230515 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Sub-subseries 2: ALSEP [Apollo Lunar Surface Experiments Package], 230501
      - ALSEP, January 1965-May 1966; 230513 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Apollo Lunar Science Program Report of Planning Teams, December 1964; 230512 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Manned Lunar Orbital Missions (Vol. L), April 1965; 230511 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Manned Lunar Orbital Missions (Vol. IA), April 1965; 230510 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - A Study of Scientific Mission Support of a Lunar Exploration System for Apollo; Final Report (Vol.III), June 16, 1965; 230509 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Scientific Mission Support Study: Apollo Extension System, July 1965; 230508 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Definition of Telemetry Equipment for Apollo Passive Lunar Scientific Experiments (TAPLE) Vol. I, Technical, August 1965; 230507 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Apollo Lunar Surface Experiments Package: Monthly Status Report, September 1965; 230506 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Space Tool Kit Survey, Development and Evaluation Program, Final Report, October 1965; 230505 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Minutes of Customer Review Meeting NASA/Manned Spacecraft Center and Space-General Corporation, ALSEP, December 15, 1965; 230504 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - ALSEP Phase I Program Progress Report No. 4, December 16, 1965; 230503 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Investigation of Lunar Surface Chemical Contamination by LEM Descent Engine and Associated Equipment, January 1966; 230502 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Apollo Telescope Mount Correspondence, 1965-1966; 230500 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Apollo Telescope Mount Correspondence, 1967; 230499 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Apollo Telescope Mount Correspondence, 1968 and n.d.; 230498 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Apollo Telescope Mount EDT's [Experiment Development Plan], 1966; 230497 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - PI's/Experiments [Principal Investigators], 230496 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ATM Preliminary Project Development Plan, July 25, 1966; 230495 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ATM Study Program Final Report, April 1, 1966; 230494 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ATM: Ball Brothers Research Corporation Material, 1964-1965; 230493 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Drawings, ATM Experiment Package Sub-Assembly, November 1966; 230492 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Astronaut Operations Requirements Document for ATM Experiment S054, February 28, 1967; 230491 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ATM Quarterly Technical Review, March 8, 1967; 230490 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Apollo Telescope Mount Subsystems-Black Box Preliminary Design, Review, October 30, 1967; 230489 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Drawings: Layout - Top Mounted TV Camera, December 1967; 230488 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ATM-WLCE [White Light Coronograph Experiment] Man-Machine Interface Review, December 12-13, 1967; 230487 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Astronaut Operations Requirements Document for Coronal XUV Spectroheliograph, Experiment S082A, December 21, 1967; 230486 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Harvard College Observatory ATM [Apollo Telescope Mount] Course Notes, Operational Material, June 1967; 230485 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Astronaut Operation Requirements Document for ATM Power System, January 2, 1968; 230484 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Apollo Telescope Mount Mission Phase Material, n.d.; 230483 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - ATM Pointing and Control Subsystem [MSFC Internal Note], 230482 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Copy, ATM Pointing Control System, AORD [Astronaut Operational Requirements Document], n.d.; 230481 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Experiments Correspondence, January-October, 1965; 230480 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Experiments Correspondence, November-December 1965; 230479 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Experiments Correspondence, January 1-7, 1966; 230478 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Experiments Correspondence, January 17-30, 1966; 230477 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Experiments Correspondence, February-March 1966; 230476 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Experiments Correspondence, April 1966; 230475 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Experiments Correspondence, October 1966 and n.d.; 230474 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Experiments Correspondence, January-May 1967; 230473 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Experiments Correspondence, June 1967-June 1968; 230472 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Apollo Subject Files, 230448
      - Biomed [Biomedical] Recorder, December 1965; 230471 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Engineering Experiments, September 1964-April 1965; 230470 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Experiments, [Handwritten notes, from binder-notebook], 1964; 230469 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - ECO [Experiments Coordination Office], July 1964-February 1965; 230468 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Experiments Group, 1966 and n.d.; 230467 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - EPO [Experiments Program Office], July-October 1965; 230466 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Experiment Proposals, 1964; 230465 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Experiment Proposals for Feasibility Review - SA 205, 1964-1965; 230464 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Experiments Review Panel, May 1964-March 1965; 230463 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Experiments Status Review, October 4, 1967; 230462 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Experiment Summaries, March 1967 and n.d.; 230461 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Film: Analysis of Radiation Damage, Space and Material on Storage and Protection, October 20, 1967, n.d.; 230460 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Illustrative Guide to Solar Activity, October 20, 1967; 230459 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Inflight Experiments Meetings, July 1964-August 1967; 230458 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - ICD [Interface Control Document], October-November 1965; 230457 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - MSFEB [Manned Space Flight Experiment Board], September 1964-July 1966; 230456 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - MSFEB [Manned Space Flight Experiment Board], September 1966-August 1963; 230455 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Medical Experiments Panel, June-December 1964; 230454 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Medical Experiments Panel, 1965; 230453 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Opportunities for Participation in Space Flight Investigations, June 1964; 230452 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Radiation (S/C), October-November 1965; 230451 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Schedules, May 1964-May 1965; 230450 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Scientific Experiments, 1964-1965; 230449 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Apollo Telescope Mount Experiments, 230443
      - ATM Experiment Proposals, 1965-1966; 230447 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - ATM Preliminary Experiment Material and Correspondence, 1967; 230446 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - ATM Experiment Material and Correspondence, 1968; 230445 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - ATM Experiments and Task Team Material, 1966-1967; 230444 (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Experiments by Number, 230412
      - AS-204 Experiments, November 1964-July 1965; 230442 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - AS-205 Experiments, March 1965-January 1967; 230441 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - AS-207 Experiments, April-November 1965; 230440 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - D-17: Solid Electrolyte Carbon Dioxide Reduction System, December 1964; 230439 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - M-12: Ergometry Experiment, February-December 1965; 230438 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - M-16: Atmosphere Turbidity Monitor for Spacecraft, June 1964-February 1965; 230437 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - M-19: Measurement of Metabolic Rate in Apollo Astronauts, February 1965; 230436 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - M-21: Effects of Long-Term Weightlessness on Vestibular Function, n.d.; 230435 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - M-509: Astronaut Maneuvering Equipment; Experiment Implementation Plan, June 1967; 230434 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - M-509: Preliminary Requirements Reviews, May and July 1968; 230433 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - M-509: Experiment Briefing, June 1968; 230432 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - M-509: Preliminary Requirements Review, August 1968; 230431 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - S-052: ATM Whitelight Coronograph, December 4, 1967; 230430 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - S-055-C: Modified Scanning Spectrometer., August 16, 1967; 230429 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - S-055-Extreme UV and X-Ray Telescope, June-September 1967; 230428 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - S-14 (Frog Otolith) and S-17 (X-Ray Astronomy) on AS-205; Operational Requirements, December 6, 1965; 230427 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - S-15: Zero-G - Single Human Cells, n.d.; 230426 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - S-16: Trapped Particle Asymmetry, June-December 1965; 230425 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - S-17: X-Ray Astronomy, December 1963-December 1965; 230424 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - S-18: Micrometeorite Collection, July 1965; 230423 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - S-19: UV Stellar Astronomy., March 1965; 230422 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - S-20: X-Ray Solar Photography, October 1965; 230421 (Box 48, Folder 5)